Jane Fonda papers SSC.MS.00477
Sophia Smith Collection
- Audiovisual materials, 1970-2014; 6; 37.88 linear feet (55 boxes)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: W.S. Hanoi Apr 3, Lake + Street Sounds, Schools, Children Playing, Leaving Troy, tails, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_334 (Reel 112)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Hanoi montage PIX, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_337 (Reel 113)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Goodbye Troy, PIX, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_340 (Reel 114)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Hanoi Sync out, PIX Heads, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_341 (Reel 115)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Hanoi April 1-4 - w/ Tra Siong + Kids-by lake-PRG Embassy-Schools-Wang Tung Ext. Interview-Leaving Troy, Sync Pix, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_343 (Reel 116)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Hanoi-Movie Studio-Interview w/ Actress-Actress in Print Shop, Sync Track Head, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_344 (Reel 117)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Binocular lifts from cut, TRK, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_350 (Reel 118)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Ha Tinh Interview w/ Tung + Quoc Sync TRK Heads, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_353 (Reel 119)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Quoc-Sync-Trk HEADS, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_354 (Reel 120)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Bomb detonation + bulldozer TRK HDS, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_356 (Reel 121)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Thanh Hoa - Bicycle Factory - Pot Factory - Man w/ Bike - Sync Pix, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_364 (Reel 122)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Thanh Hoa - Bicycle Factory - Pot Factory - Man w/ Bike - Sync Track, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_365 (Reel 123)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Numercised trims Bike Factory Thanh Hoa Pix, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_366 (Reel 124)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Numercised trims Bike Factory Thanh Hoa Trk, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_367 (Reel 125)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: TRK heads Hospital interviews w/ doctors, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_372 (Reel 126)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Camloc women/ARUN Defect-Camloc + Aitu, Sync Outs TRK Heads, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_377 (Reel 127)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Nordvietnam 1 Aug. 1972, Kopia, 70-71/2849, Engelsh|English Soundmix/ "Short" Version-To See Vietnam + Clark-/, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_400; 1 items (Ramsey Clarke note, Box 75) (Reel 128)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Engelsk An American in Hanoi-Ramses Clark 70-71/2849, Kopia, English Soundmix, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_401 (Reel 129)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Track, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_402 (Reel 130)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: 2 old viets sync torture lift, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_403 (Reel 131)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Van Trang → Arun, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 Reels (wav file) FondaFilm_408 (Reel 132)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Picture, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_416 (Reel 133)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, motion picture recording: 2 Untitled splices, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items FondaFilm_418 (Reel 134)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Thi-sync outs-TRK HEADS, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_434 (Reel 135)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Numericised trim, JJ 5000 HDS, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_438 (Reel 136)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Binocular lifts from cut, PIX, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_448 (Reel 137)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Quoc's Haskell's Joke-TRK, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_449 (Reel 138)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Hanoi Sync out, TRK Heads, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_450 (Reel 139)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Lifts from cut-2 old viets- PIX HDS, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_454 (Reel 140)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: 2 old viets sync torture lift, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_455 (Reel 141)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Introduction to the Enemy R-2A, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_457 (Reel 142)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Introduction to the Enemy R-2C, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_458 (Reel 143)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Introduction to the Enemy - R1 - Narration, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_459 (Reel 144)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Introduction to the Enemy - R2 - Narration, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_460 (Reel 145)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Introduction to the Enemy, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_461 (Reel 146)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Introduction to the Enemy - M + E #1 RII, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_462 (Reel 147)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Introduction to the Enemy - M + E #2 RII, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_463 (Reel 148)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Introduction to the Enemy RI Dialogue ST #1, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_464 (Reel 149)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Introduction to the Enemy RI Dialogue ST #2, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_465 (Reel 150)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Introduction to the Enemy Dialogue Track RII #1, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_466 (Reel 151)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Introduction to the Enemy RII Dialogue Track #2, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_467 (Reel 152)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Jane Fonda; Footage: 600; Stock: 35 mm; Roll #: 9, Originals-35 mm, Jane Fonda in NVA, 280-102 Jane Fonda, 1972 July 26; 1 items (35mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_447; 1 items (Monica Dunlap to Jane Fonda, 05 Oct 1974, Box 75) (Reel 153)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Copy of Numericised trim MOS Mrs. Chi, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_244B (Reel 154)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Kopia R1 Q.T 70-73/2373, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_412 (Reel 1-1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Kopia, R2 Q.T 70-73/2393, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_413 (Reel 1-2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Jane Fonda R1 Part 1 PRG -2, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_78 (Reel 10-1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Jane Fonda Part 2 (rolls 2-3), approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_79 (Reel 10-2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: IPC Intro to the Enemy Go In 560' prt 620, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_404 (Reel 11-1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: IPC Intro to Enemy PT 1 80' Repl sect H6851 530'-610, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_405 (Reel 11-2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: IPC Intro to Enemy PT 1 40' Repl Sect H6851 70'-110', approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_406 (Reel 11-3)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Van Trang w/ Jane + Tom, Wild Sound (C.R. H-13, H-14 + J-19), FR. S.R. #17 and S.R. #12, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_313 (Reel 12-1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: WS - For tail, Wild Sound, FR S-R #17; WS-For tail, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_314 (Reel 12-2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Jane-Vinh Linh, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_270 (Reel 13-1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Opening garble [?] Cassette #2, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_271 (Reel 13-2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Uinh Linh Cassette, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_272 (Reel 13-3)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Le Duc Tho, Pix Head, Interview R-2, CR P32, O28, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_148 (Reel 14-1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Le Duc Tho-aid → aid suffering, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_149 (Reel 14-2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Le Duc Tho, TRK Head, Interview R-2, CR P32, O28/SR 21, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_311 (Reel 15-1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Le Duc Tho-need for reconstruction, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_312 (Reel 15-2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Le Duc Tho Pix Head, Interview R-1, CR P30 + P31, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_145 (Reel 16, Item 1)
    Related manuscript is in box 88 of this collection.
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Le Duc Tho, Numericised Trim, Pix Hds, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_146 (Reel 16-2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Le Duc Tho, Numericised Trim, Heads, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_147 (Reel 16-3)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Le Duc Tho TRK Head, Interview R-1, CR P30, P31/SR. 1 + 20, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_308 (Reel 17-1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Le Duc Tho, Sync Outs, TRK + PIX Heads, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_309 (Reel 17-2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Le Duc Tho, Numericised Trim, TRK Hds, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_310 (Reel 17-3)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Van Trang Personal, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_296 (Reel 18-1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Van Trang → Arun, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_297 (Reel 18-2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Van Trang Trk Heads, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_298 (Reel 18-3)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Van Trang Trims Sync Heads, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (wav file) FondaFilm_299 (Reel 18-4)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Van Trang Personal, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_137 (Reel 19-1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Van Trang - Arun, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_138 (Reel 19-2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Van Trang - mos, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm) mov file; 1 items (FondaFilm_139) (Reel 19-3)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Van Trang Trims Sync Heads, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_140 (Reel 19-4)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Tom & Jane w/ Van Trang CR H13, H14, J19 Pix Heads, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_141 (Reel 19-5)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, audio recording: Ngainh Thi (2 taken from S 19) and Vien WS Heads, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_265 (Reel 2, Item 1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Numericised trims HDS, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_266 (Reel 2, Item 2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Untitled, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_23 (Reel 20, Item 1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: J2/25 73 74 858 231, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_24 (Reel 20, Item 2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: 160 162 163 J2/25 77 78 919 718, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_25 (Reel 20, Item 3)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: J2/25 74 233 585, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_26 (Reel 20, Item 4)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: J2/25 77 113 908, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_27 (Reel 20, Item 5)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: J2/25 74 587 656, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_28 (Reel 20, Item 6)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: 117 118 119 J2/25 74 75 727 452, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_29 (Reel 20, Item 7)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: C96 541 795, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_69 (Reel 21, Item 1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: J2/55 84 929 963, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_70 (Reel 21, Item 2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: 50 51 53 62 63 64 J2/51 44 45 825 558, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) (Reel 21, Item 3)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: J2/51 47 48 267 064, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_72 (Reel 21, Item 4)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: J2/55 45 448 863, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_73 (Reel 21, Item 5)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: J2/53 39 954 373, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_73 (Reel 21, Item 6)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Dupe keys 95 96 J2/48 22 161 299, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_54 (Reel 22, Item 1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: dupe keys to 497' 92 93, J2/48 22 301 671, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_55 (Reel 22, Item 2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: dup keys 94, J2/48, 21 22, 875 159, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_56 (Reel 22, Item 3)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: J2/47 91 92 593 389, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_57 (Reel 22, Item 4)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: 165 J2/47 98 357 944, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_58 (Reel 22, Item 5)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: 17628 29, J2/48 22 23,687 480, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_60 (Reel 22, Item 6)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Untitled, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_59 (Reel 22, Item 7)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Roll 1A, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_06 (Reel 23, Item 1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: J1/96 99, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_07 (Reel 23, Item 2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: J1/96 99 00 982 144, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_08 (Reel 23, Item 3)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: J1/94 47 784 799, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_09 (Reel 23, Item 4)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: End Crawl Title, J1 74 94 130 208 Do Not Use, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_10 (Reel 23, Item 5)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: J1/94 47 350 762, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_11 (Reel 23, Item 6)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: J1/94 47 48 800 200, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_12 (Reel 23, Item 7)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: 47 48 J1/85 44 558 972, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_14 (Reel 23, Item 9)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: J2/33 62 450 642, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_30 (Reel 24, Item 1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: 100 101 J2/33 60 204 397, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_31 (Reel 24, Item 2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: J2/33 60 398 797, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_33 (Reel 24, Item 3)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: J2/33, 63 64, 459 256, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_34 (Reel 24, Item 4)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: J2/33 11 12 366 095, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_35 (Reel 24, Item 5)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: 45 J2/33 12 096 899, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_36 (Reel 24, Item 6)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: J2/33 61 62 845 448, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_37 (Reel 24, Item 7)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: 145 146 147 148 149 150 151 152 153 J2/34 29 30 673 370, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_38 (Reel 25, Item 1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: J2/34 30 372 449, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_39 (Reel 25, Item 2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: 121 140 141 J2/34 14 15 597 009, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (mov file) FondaFilm_40 (Reel 25, Item 3)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: 93 94 95 96 97 98 J2/34 30 31 458 224, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_41 (Reel 25, Item 4)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: J2/34 31 32 268 065, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_42 (Reel 25, Item 5)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: 38 39 J2/34 14 164 580, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_43 (Reel 25, Item 6)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: 75 to 82 J2/34 28 008 800, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_44 (Reel 25, Item 7)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: 175 177 179, 359-458 to Bill F. 10-22, J2/43 33 34 359 152, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_46 (Reel 26, Item 1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: 139 72 J2/45 97 302 392, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_47 (Reel 26, Item 2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: 4 6 7 9 11 13 15 17 19 21 23 25 27, J2/44, 34 35, 745 019, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_48 (Reel 26, Item 3)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: J2/43 34 868 950, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_49 (Reel 26, Item 4)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: 176 J2/47 38 314 709, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_50 (Reel 26, Item 5)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: 120 to 128, J2/43 34 168 867, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_51 (Reel 26, Item 6)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: 136 137 138 J2/47 39 113 913, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_52 (Reel 26, Item 7)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: 131 133 134 135, J2/43 35 36 785 579, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_53 (Reel 26, Item 8)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: J2/48 20 21 899 668, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_61 (Reel 27, Item 1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: 13 246, J2/48, 25, 639 904, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_62 (Reel 27, Item 2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: J2/48 23 24 308 051, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_63 (Reel 27, Item 3)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: J2/48 84 053 377, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_64 (Reel 27, Item 4)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: J2/48 25 532 637, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_65 (Reel 27, Item 5)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: J2/48 25 408 531, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_66 (Reel 27, Item 6)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: J2/48 25 113 406, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_67 (Reel 27, Item 7)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Dup Keys 92 93 94 95 96, J2/48 21 22 711 497, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_68 (Reel 27, Item 8)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Vinh Linh Pepper Patch/Sync Pix Heads, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_123 (Reel 28, Item 1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Numericised Trims FF5000 Pix Heads, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_124 (Reel 28, Item 2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Numericised Trims FF5000 Pix Heads, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_124b (Reel 28, Item 2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: Vinh Linh Pepper Patch/Sync Trk Heads, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_262 (Reel 29, Item 1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, audio recording: Numericised trims FF 5000 Trk HDS, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 wav file) FondaFilm_126 (Reel 29, Item 2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: J1/96 28 29 931 293, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_16 (Reel 3, Item 1)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: 141 142 143 J1/97 23 028 440, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_17 (Reel 3, Item 2)
  - Introduction the the Enemy, video recording: R2/5-8, J1/96 29 294 729, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (1 mov file) FondaFilm_18 (Reel 3, Item 3)